-What are you doing? -I reorganized the fridge.
你在做什麼？ 我重新整理過冰箱
See? Bottom shelf, meats and dairy.
最底下放肉跟奶製品
Middle shelf,fruits and vegetables.
中間放水果蔬菜
And top shelf,expired products.
最上面放過期食物
Why are you doing this?
你吃飽撐著啊？
Because I'm bored out of my mind.
因為我無聊到快抓狂了
I've already been to the bank, post office and dry cleaners.
我已經去過 銀行、郵局、乾洗店
Dude,you just described seven days' worth of stuff.
老兄，你做完我一周的工作
Spread it out a little. Haven't you ever been unemployed?
你要放輕鬆一點 難道你從來沒失業過？
I'm not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical.
我不是失業 只是進修中（有安息之意）
Hey,don't get religious on me,okay?
少跟我傳教
A guy in your position needs to be better at relaxing.
你應該練習放輕鬆
That's why we have comfortable chairs. Here,sit down.
不然我們家怎麼會有安樂椅？ 過來…坐下
Ready? Watch.
準備好沒？仔細看了
And then....
然後…真好
-So,what? We just sit? -Oh,no,no.
就光坐著？ 當然不是
We're not gonna just sit. Watch.
不只是坐著 看好了
-Hello,Chandler Bing. -Hello,Mr. Bing.
我是錢德賓 賓先生
I love you.
我愛你
All right,whoever this is, stop calling me!
不管你是誰，別再打了
It's been 6 months! It's not funny!
你已經騷擾我半年 一點也不好笑
I can see you, Mr. Bing.
賓先生，我看得到你
You look sexy in your new suit.
你穿新西裝真性感
Leave me alone! For the love of God, leave me alone!
求你行行好，別再騷擾我了
And that's Wednesday.
這只是週三的樂子
The One with The lnappropriate Sister
本集播出：「情比兄妹深」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey,you guys! Guess what?
告訴你們
The British are coming?
英國人要打來啦？
Oh,you and your ways.
你的笑話真冷
Since it's Christmas, I'm going to be collecting donations.
耶誕節快到了 我要負責去樂捐募款
I have my bell and later on I get my bucket.
我已經拿到鈴鐺 過幾天就能拿到募捐筒
I'll be spreading joy to the people.
我要散播歡樂給大家
Last year I spread a little joy, but not enough.
去年散播的不夠多
So this year I'm doing the whole city.
今年一定要讓全紐約 都感受到
I knew a girl in high school who did that. She was very popular.
我有個高中同學也跟你一樣 她很紅
It's weird,you're starting to sound a lot like Chandler lately.
怪了，你口氣跟錢德越來越像
That is so not true.
胡說八道
So,Phoebe,where are you doing your bell-ringing?
菲比，你要去哪裡搖鈴？
They gave me a great spot right by Macy's.
我分到梅西百貨旁當紅位子
They never give a good spot to a rookie...
新人很少分到這位子
...but I'm the only one who can say "Merry Christmas" in 25 languages.
可是只有我會用25種語言 說耶誕快樂
I lied!
我唬人的
Oh,my God. Here's Danny.
天啊，丹尼在那邊
Just watch this.
你們看
See? Still pretending he's not interested.
看見沒？還在假裝對我沒興趣
He's coming over. Pretend we've forgotten who he is.
他走過來了，大家裝不認識他 忘記他是誰
-Hey,guys. -Hey,Danny.
你們好 丹尼
Oh,Danny! Hey!
丹尼
You know Rachel. She's nice. She's not bad to look at,right?
丹尼，你認得瑞秋吧 她人很好，長得也不賴吧？
Thanks,Mon.
謝了，摩妮卡
Of course.
當然啦
Do you want to go out on a date with her?
你要不要跟她約會？
Absolutely. Is Friday okay?
好啊，週五可以嗎？
Friday is perfect. She can't wait.
非常好，她等不及要赴約
On the date,I'll be able to talk to her directly?
約會時 我可以直接跟她說話吧？
See you Friday.
週五見
Okay,what the hell was that? You know what? Don't answer me.
你搞什麼？ 算了，不用說了
I have a date with Danny!
我要跟丹尼約會咯
All right,it's 4:30, I guess my lunch break is over.
已經4點半，午休該結束了
-What are you guys gonna do? -lf you're going back to work...
你們等下要幹麼？ 既然你要回去上班
...I'll probably just hang out. You know,make some calls.
我們大概一起打幾個電話吧 真不錯
How could I not get the part?
我怎麼會落選？
The play was about a 29-year-old ltalian actor from Queens!
主角就是出身皇后區的 29歲意大利演員
Well,Talia Shire suddenly became available.
泰莉雅雪兒突然有空
She's a woman!
她是歐巴桑耶
What can I say? She nailed it!
你要我說什麼？ 人家就是有辦法
Is there anything else?
好吧，還有什麼戲份？
You'll just say no again,but...
你一定又會拒絕…
...gay porn?
同性戀A片？
Happy holidays!
佳節快樂
Feliz Navidad!
耶誕快樂（西班牙文）
Allo and Merry Christmas!
嗨（法文），耶誕快樂
Oh,thank you,sir! Here's some joy.
謝謝你，祝你幸福
-How's it going? -It's going okay.
我來看看你做得如何 很順利
Good. Let me help you out.
那好，我順便捐點錢
Oh,thanks!
謝謝 甭客氣
Is that a new suede jacket? It looks really expensive.
新的鹿皮外套？好像很貴
Yeah. I guess.
是不便宜
Just get your nails done?
你剛去做指甲？
Yes,Phoebe,but this is all I have,okay?
對，我只剩這些錢了
Thanks. Happy holidays! Here's your joy.
謝啦，佳節快樂，祝你幸福
Thank you! Happy holidays and Wait.
謝謝，佳節愉快 等等
-You can't take money out. -I'm making change for the bus.
只能捐錢不能拿 我跟你換零錢搭公車
Can't you leave the dollar for the poor?
拿零錢就好 其他錢是要救濟窮人的
I'm poor. I gotta take the bus.
我就是窮人，而且還得搭公車
Okay,season's greetings and everything, but still
佳節愉快，可是你不能…
Bite me, blondie!
咬我啊，小妞
I'm going to give him something besides joy. Just
除了祝他幸福，我還要…
I can't believe I didn't get that part.
那個角色根本就是為我而寫 結果我竟然落選
I'm sorry,man.
很遺憾
What you should do...
你知道該怎麼做嗎？
...is make something happen for yourself.
你要自己創造機會
You know, like write a play.
例如寫個電影劇本
Or a movie. What about those Good Will Hunting guys?
或者拍部電影 就像「心靈捕手」那兩個
Be realistic,you know? If I did write something...
羅斯，少作白日夢了 就算我寫出劇本
...what are the chances I could get those guys to star in it?
哪有辦法請到他們？
Wait a second. I could star in it!
有了，我可以自己主演
Or that.
也可以
I can't write. I mean,I'm an actor.
我不會寫劇本 我是演員
I could act like a writer. Here....
我可以裝成編劇
But see? Nada.
不過…什麼也寫不出來
I don't have the discipline that it takes. I can't do it.
我不像編劇一樣有紀律 我辦不到
I'll help you.
我可以幫你
Yeah. I'll make up a schedule and make sure you stick to it.
幫你訂出時間表 盯著你乖乖照做
Plus,it'll give me something to do.
我自己也有事做了
You'd do that for me? Thanks.
真的？你願意幫我？
We'll start slow. All you have to come up with tonight...
對 謝謝 一開始慢慢來 今晚之前...
...is the name of your main character.
...只要想好主角名字
-Done. -And it can't be Joey.
好了 不可以是喬伊
-It's not. -Or Joseph.
不是 也不能是約瑟夫
What's up?
你怎麼啦？
I just saw Danny on the subway with a girl...
我剛看到丹尼跟女生搭地鐵
...and he had his arm around her.
他還摟著她
Honey,I'm sorry.
我真為你難過
You should be. This is all your fault.
你的確該難過，一切都要怪你
You meddled in our relationship!
誰叫你插手我們的感情世界
You had no relationship!
你們根本沒在一起
But I was doing my thing and everything...
不過我已經擬好計劃
...was going according to the plan!
一切都按部就班進行中
Oh, God, stop with the plan!
拜託 別再提你的鳥計劃
So what if you saw him with a girl?
你看到他跟女生在一起又如何
That doesn't mean anything.
那不代表什麼
You'll go out with Danny and be so charming he'll forget all about...
你就快跟丹尼約會 到時你可以火力全開
...that stupid subway girl.
迷得他忘記地鐵那個蠢妞
She was kind of stupid.
那女生的確傻里傻氣
You're right. I'm just going to go on the date.
你說得對 好，我就去約會
I'm just going to go on the date. That is the new plan.
我會去赴約 這就是我的新計劃
Hurry!
快點
-How do you spell "suspicious"? -Why?
「多疑」怎麼寫？ 幹嘛？
I think this character is going to be suspicious about stuff.
因為這個角色很「多疑」
Yes!
帥！
Chandler Bing, seven! Chandler Bing, zero!
錢德賓7分，錢德賓0分
You're driving me crazy with that.
看你玩那個都快讓我抓狂了
-I'll stop. -Don't stop.
我不玩就是了 繼續玩
Move the bowl further away. Ross could make that shot.
碗拿遠一點 連羅斯都投得進
Well, you suck. But at least you suck at a man's game now.
真是遜斃了 不過至少你進了成人組
-Want to play? -I can't play games.
要不要玩？ 我不能跟你玩
Ross'll be home soon. I have to write five pages to stick to his schedule.
羅斯就快回來了 按照他的時間表 我應該寫完5頁
So play for 30 minutes, then write until he gets home.
你可以先玩30分鐘 再繼續用功到他回家
All right.
好吧
But listen,what do you say we...
不過
...crank it up a notch?
規則應該更困難
I'm intrigued.
願聞其詳
All right. All we need is a little lighter fluid.
要先找到可燃性液體
But be careful. I want our security deposit back.
好，不過你小心點 我還想拿回房租押金
We said goodbye to that when we invented hammer darts.
我們發明鐵錘標槍時 就拿不回來了
Do you even remember which part of the wall is not spackle?
你記得哪面牆壁沒補過嗎？ 記得，這裡
Thank you! Happy holiday.
謝謝，佳節愉快
No,that's trash,young lady. You can't
小姐，那可是垃圾，不可以…
Stop that young lady! She donated trash!
別這樣，小姐，她竟然捐垃圾
The charity's on fire!
樂捐筒著火了
Help! Thank you. I need that!
來人啊 謝謝，我正需要
What is this?
那是什麼鬼東西？
It's 9:00 in the morning!
現在才早上9點耶
All right. "A room."
我看看，場景，房間
"A man enters. He looks suspicious."
一名男子滿臉狐疑地走進來
That's it?
就這樣？
You're supposed to have five pages done by now...
喬伊，你今天應該寫5頁
...including an exciting incident.
還包括一個高潮
What is all this? "The Official Rulebook of Fireball."
這是什麼垃圾？ 大火球遊戲規則
That's the game we played.
我們剛在玩這遊戲
It's great. You take a tennis ball,a bowl and lighter
很好玩，道具就是一顆網球 一個碗、可燃液體
This is helping your career? You wanted to be an actor.
這對你的事業有幫助嗎？我還以為你想當演員
Not the creator of "Crazy Lawsuit Game."
不是發明危險遊戲被人告
You're right. I'll get back to work.
你說得對，我該工作了
Shame on you! You should know better! Joey needs to work.
你真不應該，還帶壞他 明知道喬伊應該要工作
Now come on.
振作點
You can have this back when the five pages are done.
等你寫完5頁才還你
-I had a nice time tonight. -So did l.
我今晚很開心 我也是
I'm really glad Monica asked us out.
幸好摩妮卡約我們出來
I'd love to ask you in, but my sister's visiting.
我很想請你進去 不過我妹來住我家
-I think she's asleep on the couch. -Your sister?
她可能睡在沙發上了 你妹妹？
Your sister's asleep on the couch?
睡在沙發上？
I saw you with her on the subway and now she's asleep on the couch!
我上次看到你們搭地鐵 現在她還睡在你沙發
-I thought I heard you. -Hey,great,you're up.
我就猜是你 太好了，你起床了
Rachel,my sister Krista.
瑞秋，這是我妹妹克莉絲塔
Nice to meet you.
很高興認識你
I wish you'd warned me. I'd have fixed myself up.
你應該告訴我要帶朋友回來 害我穿得邋裡邋遢
-Like it would help. -You are so bad.
有差嗎？ 你真惡劣
-You are. -You are.
你才是 是你
-You are. -You are!
是你 是你
You are so dead.
你完蛋了
I'm gonna get you. Come here!
我要教訓你一頓
It's very nice to meet you.
很高興認識你
Nobody! Nobody respects the bucket!
沒有人，沒一個人尊重募捐筒
You wouldn't believe what people put in here!
大家都丟些莫名其妙的東西
Does this look like a garbage can to you?
你覺得這像垃圾桶嗎？
Does it look like an ashtray?
不像 像煙灰缸嗎？
Does it look like a urinal?
不像 像尿桶嗎？
-So you going back out there? -Yeah, but I won't take any more crap.
菲比，你還要回去募捐嗎？ 當然，不過我受夠了
No more Mrs. Nice Bucket.
再也不當募捐好好小姐
Good. You're tough. You lived on the street.
加油，你在街上流浪過，夠悍
I'll go back to being Street Phoebe.
我要當回強人菲比
But not totally back. Street Phoebe wouldn't be friends with you guys.
不過也不能一模一樣 否則才不會鳥你們 抱歉啦
Can I ask you guys something?
可以問個問題嗎？ 當然
I don't have brothers,so I don't know, but did you guys wrestle?
我沒有兄弟，實在不暸解 你們會打來打去嗎？
-Oh,yeah. -All the time.
當然會 常常
In fact,I was undefeated.
而且我從沒輸過
Well,you weighed 200 pounds.
因為你以前90多公斤
Still,I was quick as a cat.
不過我還是跟貓咪一樣矯捷
I met Danny's sister yesterday.
我昨天碰到丹尼的妹妹
-That was the girl on the subway. -You're kidding.
就是跟他一起搭地鐵的那個 真的假的？
They were very,you know...
他們非常…
...wrestle-y.
...會扭打
But I guess that's normal?
這樣正常嗎？
We don't wrestle now.
我們現在不會這樣了
Not since I got too strong for you.
自從我長大變壯後就不打了
Too strong for me?
長大變壯？ 對
You wanna go right now?
你要比劃一下嗎？
I'll take you right now,buddy! You wanna go?
我可以立刻打敗你，信不信？
Oh,fine.
沒問題
Ready?
預備
Wrestle!
開始
Okay,you know what?
這個嘛…很好
Actually,that helps a lot. Thanks.
謝謝你們幫了大忙
Let's go! The puck drops in 20 minutes!
趕快走，20分後就要開打了 喬伊，快點
Joey's not going.
喬伊不能去
I didn't finish my five pages.
我還沒寫完5頁
Finish them tomorrow.
明天再寫不就成了？
Tomorrow he's redoing yesterday's pages.
因為他明天要修改昨天的5頁
Yesterday's pages did not reflect my best work.
我昨天寫的有待改進
Cut him some slack. If he relaxes, he'll get some work done.
別再逼他，讓他透口氣 搞不好會寫得更好
I think he's been relaxing enough, thanks to you...
他已經透夠多氣了 這都要感謝你跟...
...and Fireball.
...大火球
If you think Fireball's relaxing, you've never played.
玩大火球可是很緊張 顯然你沒玩過
You're doing this because you're bored.
你拚命壓搾喬伊 是因為你自己沒事做
It's not his fault you're unemployed.
又不是喬伊害你失業的
I am not unemployed. I'm on sabbatical!
我不是失業，只是進修中
Guys,don't fight.
你們別吵架
And I'm doing this because I am Joey's friend.
我之所以這麼做 是因為我是喬伊的朋友
If you were a friend, you'd be doing the same.
如果你也是他朋友 就該學學我
So being a friend means being a jerk?
當朋友就得這麼混帳？
If it does,then you're an amazing friend of mine.
要是真如你所說 你可真是我第一號好友
Let's settle this over a game of Fireball.
別吵了，大家玩場大火球 別氣了
-I'll unhook the smoke detectors. -Let's settle this right now.
我去拆掉防火警鈴 現在就一了百了
There. Now no one's going to the game.
好了，誰也不准去
-I paid for those! -You said you would,but you didn't.
門票是我買的 才怪，你每次都說要付錢 卻一次也沒吐過錢
Oh,yeah.
也對
We finally get to the top of the mountain...
我們終於爬到山頂
...and airhead here forgets the camera.
結果這個笨蛋竟然忘了相機
The same thing happened to me one time.
我也發生過這種事情
When did that happen to you?
什麼時候？
Remember? We were jogging and saw that bird.
上次我們不是到公園慢跑 看到小鳥
I wanted to take a picture, but I didn't have my camera.
我想拍下來 竟然沒帶相機
Chasing the churro guy is not jogging.
也對，不過追小販可不算慢跑
Oh,this is so good. You have got to try it.
超好吃，你一定要吃一口
-Damn. I got it on my pants. -Here,I'll get it.
糟糕，褲子沾到了 我來擦
We better take them off or the stain will set.
最好上樓換件褲子 否則以後洗不掉
-I want to wear them tonight. -Oh,great.
而且我今晚約會還要穿 真好
Okay, bye. Oh,my God!
再見，天哪
-That was unbelievable. -See? I told you.
不可思議 看吧，我早說過了
Yeah. Sorry.
可憐的瑞秋
I don't believe they're brother and sister.
我不相信他們是兄妹
They're brother and sister?!
他們是兄妹？
I guess you'll have to cancel your date.
看來你得取消約會了
And call their mother.
而且還要打電話給他們老媽
「非尿桶」
「我沒有百貨公司簡介」
Wait a minute. Open your hand. Let me take a look.
等一下，手張開給我檢查
Quarter,dime. Lint? Not interested in that.
兩毛五、一毛、線頭？不要
What's this? A Canadian coin?
這是什麼？加拿大硬幣？
Get out of here!
滾
No drinks near the bucket.
不准在募捐筒旁邊喝東西
Set it down there and then you can make a contribution.
先放在那邊才准捐款
You can leave the "hurt bunny" look over there too.
少裝一副可憐兮兮的樣子
Hi,Bob.
嗨，鮑柏
I thought I told you to get out of here!
不是叫你滾了嗎？
Phoebe,we've been getting complaints.
菲比，我們接到申訴
-We're moving you to a less high-profile spot. -What？
上面要調你離開 什麼？
-Ginger's taking this corner. -That chick can't handle my corner.
以後這裡由金傑負責 這小妞才沒這能耐
Look, either you leave or we remove you.
你不走，我們就得趕你走
Fine.
好
I'll give you one pointer. Look out for that bitch.
勸你一句，注意那個臭婆娘
-I thought we said 7. -You know what? Let's skip it.
瑞秋，不是約7點嗎？ 今天就算了
What? Why?
什麼？為什麼？
You and your sister seem to have a very special bond
你們兄妹似乎…非常要好
Oh,great. That "special bond" again.
太好了，又說這句話
Why do women have a problem with my being close to my sister?
我跟我妹感情好 又是哪裡讓女人看不順眼了？
-I don't know, but..  -Do you have brothers?
聽我說，我不知道事實真相 你有兄弟嗎？
No,I have two sisters. But one has a very masculine energy.
我有兩個妹妹 其中一個很像男人婆
-Are you close? -No. They're not very nice people.
你們要好嗎？ 沒有，她們不是好人
I like you. I think this could go somewhere.
我很喜歡你 應該可以順利交往
So I'm close to my family. Don't let it stand in our way.
我是跟家人感情深厚 你就為了這點不鳥我？
Well,I don't know....
我也不知道…
When you put it that way
聽你這麼說也有道理
Danny? Hurry up. The bath's getting cold.
丹尼 快點 洗澡水快涼了
-What？ -I'll see you later.
又怎麼了？ 我先走了
There's some kids playing in the street.
路上有小孩在玩耍
Want to go give them a project, ruin their day?
你要不要去叫他們寫作業 毀了他們的一天？
If they have a ball, you could stick razors in it...
如果你手邊有球 就可以插上剃刀
...and teach them a new game: "Gonna-Need-Stitches Ball."
教他們玩「殺人球」
Hey,guys! I was at the library. I already finished my five pages.
我整個早上都待在圖書館 已經寫完今天的5頁了
Now we can go to the Ranger game last night!
那我們可以去看昨晚的騎兵隊比賽了
No,dude. Ross tore up the tickets.
不行，門票給羅斯撕掉了
I guess without so many distractions it's easier for you to focus?
沒有讓你分心的事情 就比較容易專心吧？
Also without somebody breathing down your neck all the livelong day!
沒人整天跟在你屁股後面 也比較得心應手吧？
The important thing is, I finished it. And I think it's really good.
隨便你們說，總之我寫完了 而且寫得還不錯
But it would help if I could hear it. Would you guys read it for me?
不過你們幫忙念台詞 才是幫大忙 可不可以念一下？
-Yeah,all right. -All right.
好吧 好
"It's a typical New York apartment.
「一間普通的紐約公寓」
Two guys are hanging out."
「兩個男人正在家裡」，羅斯
"Hey,man."
嗨
"What is up?"
有什麼事？
"About yesterday. I was really wrong. I am sorry."
昨天是我錯了，對不起
"No,it was me. I'm sorry. I overreacted."
我才該道歉，我反應過頭了
"Maybe it was both of us. But we had our best friend's inter
或許我們都有錯 反正我們都是為了朋友…
But we had our best friend's interest at heart."
我們都是為了朋友好
"Could I be more sorry?"
我非常不好意思
"l don't know. I am one sorry...
我才是該道歉的...
...polontologist."
...古生物學家
All right, Joey, we get it.
喬伊，我們懂了
-I'm sorry. -I'm sorry too.
對不起 我也該道歉
Keep reading. The good part's coming up.
你們要繼續讀下去 精采的才要上場，繼續念
"l am sorry, Chandler."
對不起，錢德
"l am sorry, Ross."
對不起，羅斯
"A handsome man enters."
「帥哥上場」
"l don't know what you're talking about, but I'd like to thank you both.
不知道你們在扯什麼 不過我要向你們兩位道謝
You. You wouldn't let me give up on myself.
你讓我不放棄自己
And you.
你
You co-created Fireball."
你與我一起創造了大火球
"The End."
「劇終」
This took you all day?
這就花了你一整天？
No, this took five minutes.
沒有，我只寫了5分鐘
I spent the rest of the day coming up with new Ultimate Fireball!
其他時間都在寫 「終極大火球」遊戲規則
It's a typical New York apartment. Two girls are just hanging out. Go.
場景在一般紐約公寓 屋內有兩個女生
-"Hi,how are you doing,Kelly?" -"I'm doing just fine.
嗨，凱莉，你好嗎？ 我很好
God, Tiffany, you smell so great."
提芬妮，你今天好香
"It's my new perfume.
我噴了新香水
Why don't you come closer where you can really appreciate it?"
你過來一點才聞得仔細
-Joey,you are sick. -This is disgusting.
喬伊，你這大變態 惡斃了
I'm not reading this.
我才不要念哩
Wait,wait,wait! The handsome man was about to enter!
什麼？ 等等，帥哥才剛要上場